http://www.goggo.com/signup/privacyPolicy.html

Privacy Policy
Everyone.net™ Incorporated ("Everyone.net") agrees to abide by
this Privacy Policy with respect to information gathered on web
pages hosted by Everyone.net. Such information is being received
by both Everyone.net and the Partner through which Everyone.net
provides its services to you. You should contact the Partner to
determine the privacy policy, if any, which applies to Partner's
collection and use of such information. However, in no event shall
Everyone.net be liable for Partner's use or disclosure of such
information.
The terms "we" and "us" refer to Everyone.net.
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy
we provide this notice explaining our online information practices
and the choices you can make about the way your information is
collected and used.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected on the Everyone.net
web site, or submitted to Everyone.net at any time through any
web pages which we host.
Personally Identifiable Information - When visiting Everyone.net's
or any Partner's web site and signing up for or using Everyone.net
services through a web page hosted by us, you may choose to supply
Everyone.net with information that identifies you personally.
For end-users, this information may include your name and contact information,
gender, age group, occupation and industry, and user-comments
and opt-in preference; we intend to collect shipping and billing
information, which may, in the future, include credit card numbers,
and other payment types of information. We also intend to collect
behavior patterns, which may include recording frequency of use
of our services, which and when items were purchased, at which
site and page, and other information related to behavior patterns.
We collect prospect information, which may include name, and contact information
of individual(s) you think would be interested in our services.
For Partners, the information we collect may include your name and contact
information, your site's category, your web site information (URL,
visitors per day, description of services offered at web site),
and user-comments.
When Partners add our services to their web site, end-user information
collected is stored in our database. Thus, our database has information
collected on our site as well as on Partner sites. As stated in
the Partner and End-User agreements, Everyone.net and each Partner
both have access to the information specific to their site only;
individual Partners do not have the ability to access information
about end-users from other Partner sites. The information Everyone.net
collects will be used as stated below. As for each of our Partners, they will determine what they will do with the information collected, while each
have individually agreed to abide by this Privacy Policy, the
Everyone.net Partner Agreement and End-User Agreement.
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself or others to
complete the transaction for which it is intended. This may include
administering a service such as email, search, community, e-commerce,
etc., completing an order, shipping a product, or contacting you
if you have indicated your permission to do so. We do not share
this information with outside parties without your permission
except to the extent that is necessary to administer the services
we offer our Partners and end-users.
When we receive subscribed email addresses or get messages posted
on our support forum, we use the return email addresses to reply
with the information requested. For subscribed email addresses, we will email with service announcements and updates as requested.
Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not
shared with outside parties.
For end-users, when supplying name and contact information, shipping information,
prospect information, and user-comments to Everyone.net, we will
use it to answer your questions, ship your products, or provide
you with the requested services. When supplying name and contact
information to Everyone.net you can indicate your preference if
you would like to be contacted to receive information and updates
about Everyone.net's or Partner's services, or special offers
from other companies through the Everyone.Benefits!™ program.
In addition, when indicating your age, gender, occupation and
industry, and contact information, we will extract non-identifying
and aggregate information to better design our web site and services,
and to share the aggregate data with advertisers. For example,
we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited
a certain area on our web site, or that Y number of men and Z
number of women use a certain service. Everyone.net services may
also utilize personally identifiable end-user information to provide
targeted content and commerce opportunities to end-users based
on their demographic and behavioral information. Also, we may
use this information to gather aggregate behavioral patterns such
as frequency of use of our services, interests, types of items
purchased, how many items purchased, etc., to administer and improve
our services accordingly.
For Partners, when supplying name and contact information, site's category,
web site information (such as URL address, visitors per day, description
of services offered at web site), and user-comments, we will put
this into aggregate information so we can categorize and understand
the types of web sites that use our services, and also to administer
our services. Also, we will use this information to respond to
your requests as well as to contact you for general business purposes.
For example, if you forget your account information, we will use
this information to verify you are the account holder.
For prospects, when getting information about you, we will use the information
for which it was intended or submitted. You have the right to
access and correct information submitted about you, receive the
same courteous and professional treatment and services as our
end-users and Partners.
Finally, for end-users, Partners, and prospects, we never use or share the personally identifiable information
provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described
above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or
otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Conditional Access Area-Control Center
Everyone.net maintains an area called the "Control Center" which
is an admin tool that allows you to administer the services you
set up through Everyone.net. To access the Control Center, you
will need to enter an account ID and password. In order to sign
up for an account, you will need to provide your name and contact
information, your site's category, your web site information (URL,
visitors per day, description of services offered at web site),
etc.
Online Support Forum
When using the online "Support" forum of our web site to post
your questions and/or comments, you will be asked to indicate
your name, email address, and message. When posting your message,
your name, email address, and message are publicly displayed and
available to anyone who may visit those pages.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure
the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate
physical, electronic, and managerial procedures reasonably designed
to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
The Control Center and end-user accounts have SSL (Secure Socket
Layer) encryption to secure personal identification. In addition,
personnel who have access to our database are trained to maintain
and secure all information.
Everyone.net has teamed up with Above.net to provide a faster
Internet connection from our servers. As a result, our servers
are now co-located at Above.net's facility. Above.net does not
have the ability to access our servers or any information stored
in our servers. Also, our servers are secured in a locked and
alarmed facility to protect all our equipment and data.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Information
For Partners, you can access all your personally identifiable information
that Everyone.net collects online and maintains by logging into
your password-protected (SSL encrypted) account at http://www.everyone.net and selecting to update your "Profile." For end-users, you can access your information by logging into your password-protected
end-user account and selecting to update your "Personal Info."
We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You
can also correct factual errors in your personally identifiable
information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
If you do not currently have an account with us, and have submitted
information on our site, you can access and correct the information
that we maintain by contacting us.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable
steps to verify your identity before granting access or making
corrections.
How to Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy
policies, please call us at 408-519-8200 or send us an email at
privacypolicy@everyone.net.
Email, Search and Community Specific Terms and Conditions
Everyone.net considers email transmitted via our service to be
the private correspondence between the sender and recipient. Therefore,
we will not monitor, edit or disclose the contents of your private
communications, except as provided in the End User Agreement.
Content posted to public community areas is publicly available
and Everyone.net reserves the right to remove any publicly posted
content which is objectionable.
Free Email.
Copyright © 2002 Goggo.com (Gee-Oh Gee-Gee Oh! Dot Com).
Privacy Policy.
 
